It's interesting how people often really
like the managers and the higher-ups who
can laugh at themselves and who don't
mind other people making jokes at their
expense. [music] It's so kind of
backwards, isn't it? It's like showing
that you don't care about being
respected is very admirable and worthy
of respect. But it depends what it is, I
suppose. Because it's like if it's jokes
and that's the whole thing of if you're
towing the line where it's clearly still
a joke, [music] then it's fine. But if
you're actually being disrespectful,
that's a different thing. And that's the
whole gray area of British humor and
what is okay and what is actually rude.
>> It's It's funny you mention that cuz I I
had a habit of um
>> [laughter]
>> if there were work parties, they usually
they give you free alcohol. So,
obviously I took full advantage of that
and used to get really drunk. And then I
would end up kind of like making jokes
with like people way more senior than
me. And I always would worry the next
day like, "Oh, did I say something that
was like too far or a joke too far or
whatever?" But nothing ever
nothing ever happened, you know? It was
But it's always like a risk that yeah,
if you like sort of joking around with
them, it can backfire. Like I remember
when I worked in Dubai, I did make a
joke to two of the bosses about being
late all the time.
Which is a bit like
>> [laughter]
>> could be taken in a very bad way.
>> That's quite amazing, isn't it? That
like you felt comfortable to make that
sort of joke. In a lot of contexts and a
lot of cultures, you would never ever
like expose your own flaw.
>> Well, absolutely. Like it is certainly
even in the Middle East, I think there's
a a little bit more of a culture of
hierarchy compared to the UK. And you
don't want to kind of step on anyone's
toes, so to speak. So, I did worry when
I said that. I was like, "Oh god, I've
said the wrong thing." But they
genuinely didn't care. They just laughed
and then it was like anything else, so
>> Well, yeah. Worst case, they would just
agree with you and maybe feel a bit
embarrassed.
>> I think if someone took it the wrong
way, you're kind of in their bad books.
So, I did [music] worry that like,
"God." But anyway, it was fine in the
end. Maybe I was overthinking it, but
Yes.
>> But see see that sort of joke, if it
landed correctly, it could have made the
two of you closer. You feel like, "Oh,
you know, we can all see each other's
problems and it's all fine." And then
you've just like Yeah, you've got a new
level of your friendship then.
>> Yeah, exactly. That's the trade-off. So,
it's a very difficult um it's a diff-
it's a very difficult thing.
>> [music]